<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<reunion xmlns="http://schemas.assemblee-nationale.fr/referentiel" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:type="reunionCommission_type">
  <uid>RUANR5L16S2023IDC449377</uid>
  <timeStampDebut>2023-05-30T17:00:00.000+02:00</timeStampDebut>
  <lieu>
    <lieuRef xsi:nil="true"/>
    <libelleLong>Salle Colbert - Palais Bourbon</libelleLong>
  </lieu>
  <cycleDeVie>
    <etat>Confirmé</etat>
    <chrono>
      <creation>2023-07-06T00:00:00.000+02:00</creation>
      <cloture xsi:nil="true"/>
    </chrono>
  </cycleDeVie>
  <demandeur xsi:nil="true"/>
  <organeReuniRef>PO807461</organeReuniRef>
  <participants>
    <participantsInternes/>
    <personnesAuditionnees/>
  </participants>
  <visioConference>false</visioConference>
  <sessionRef xsi:nil="true"/>
  <ouverturePresse>false</ouverturePresse>
  <captationVideo>false</captationVideo>
  <ODJ>
    <convocationODJ>
      <item>Audition d’un groupe d’ONG israéliennes et palestiniennes « Coalition pour la paix ».&#13;Délégation palestinienne :&#13;Mr. Nidal Foqaha - Director General of PPC, Palestinian Peace Coalition, Geneva Initiative Palatine&#13;Dr. Shaddad Attili - former Water Minister and member of the Negotiations Affairs Department&#13;Mr. Asharaf Ajrami – Director of Al-Damour Center (former Minister of Prisoners)&#13;Mrs. Sahar Qawasmi, Director General of Adwar for Social Change&#13;Mrs. Frihan Farrah, Coordinator, INMAA for Development&#13;Ms. Rana Salman, Combatants for Peace, Palestine&#13;Mrs. Issa Maram, Hope Flower School&#13;Ms. Reem Jarrar, Coordinator of the Two State Coalition – Palestinian Side&#13;&#13;Délégation israélienne :&#13;Mr. Gadi Baltiansky - Director General - Geneva Initiative&#13;Mrs. Yudith Oppenheimer - Executive Director, Ir Amim&#13;Mr. Ido Dembin - Molad - the Center for the Renewal of Israeli Democracy.&#13;Mr. Lior Amihai - Director General - Peace Now&#13;Mr Nadav Tamir - Director - Jstreet&#13;Mr. Yariv Oppenheimer - Director, The Israeli Tow State Coalition&#13;Mrs. Elisheva Mikowsky - Co-Director Peace and Conciliation Department - Achord Center - Social Psychology for Social Change&#13;Dr. Michal Slitranick - Civil Rights and Human Rights Law, Senior member of the Law Professors Forum for Democracy.</item>
    </convocationODJ>
    <resumeODJ>
      <item>Audition d’un groupe d’ONG israéliennes et palestiniennes « Coalition pour la paix ».</item>
    </resumeODJ>
    <pointsODJ/>
  </ODJ>
  <compteRenduRef xsi:nil="true"/>
  <formatReunion>Ordinaire</formatReunion>
  <infosReunionsInternationale>
    <estReunionInternationale>true</estReunionInternationale>
    <listePays>
      <paysRef>GOP756447</paysRef>
    </listePays>
  </infosReunionsInternationale>
</reunion>
